Hannah Mulligan

312-956-6112 | North Wales, PA | hannahmulligan87@gmail.com | <u>LINKEDIN</u> | <u>GITHUB</u>

SUMMARY

Coffee and code are the words to best describe my talents and interests. However, my passion lies in helping people through implementing creative solutions to connect people with the experiences that make life fulfilling. My detail-orientated nature, insatiable hunger to learn, and undying drive have allowed me to extend beyond my comfort zone and achieve new goals that I had once not thought possible.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Python, Java, MERN, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Django, Flask, Spring, MySQL, NoSQL, Bootstrap

TECHNICAL PROJECTS

Coffee Passport | Full-Stack Python | Git demo

Virtual way to connect and diversify your coffee tastes

- Created my project using Django in order to simplify and increase connectivity during coffee tastings
- Designed the front-end from scratch to create a friendly user interface

Olivo Medical Wellness Centers | Front-End | Live Site

Solving this practice's problem of missing traffic and new customers due to lack of web presence.

- Built the web presence from scratch using front-end development improved traffic of new customers allowing the practice to implement telemedicine as a new service.
- Optimized discoverability through SEO, Google analytics, and Google Business resulting an increase in web traffic.

IL-PAMS | Front-End | Live Site

Helped this non-profit to automate member involvement as well as to localize news and upcoming events

- Built the web presence from scratch using front-end development improved traffic of new members and donors.
- Optimized discoverability through SEO, Google analytics, and Google Business resulting an increase in web traffic.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Barista - Shift Supervisor - Assistant Store Manager | *Starbucks* | Chicago, IL - Warrington, PA - Huntingdon Valley, PA

- Recommended a modification in inventory supply increasing customer satisfaction
- Strengthed and developed my team through rotational working plans minimizing partner burnout
- Partner of the Quarter
- Increased customer relations on a quantifiable scale by 54%

Associate - Crew Lead | AMC Theaters | Chicago, IL - Neshaminy, PA

2018-2019

- Coached organized team plans resulting in an increase in ticket and food sales
- Employee of the month June 2018, June 2019

Office Staff | Olivo Wellness | Chicago, IL

2018-2019

Managing digital media and accounting records resulting an increase in targeted advertising and traffic

Volunteer | IL-PAMS | Chicago, IL

2018-2019

- Updated and maintained software and sales in preparation for upcoming fundraisers.
- Managed finances and planning for an upcoming mission to Peru.

EDUCATION

Coding Dojo | Full-Stack Developer Certificate

2021-2022

• Immersive Full-Stack Training Program in Python, Java, and MERN